<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Terraform on Sarah French</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/tags/terraform/</link><description>Recent content in Terraform on Sarah French</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sarahfrench.dev/tags/terraform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Debugging Terraform providers with VS Code</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2024-05-28-debugging-terraform-providers-with-vscode/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2024-05-28-debugging-terraform-providers-with-vscode/</guid><description>My first experience of &amp;lsquo;debugging&amp;rsquo; was using good old console.log in JavaScript when I was first learning about programming. Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that print statements and logs only get you so far, and proper debugging is so much more useful. When I first started contributing to Terraform provider projects I wasn&amp;rsquo;t shown how to use debuggers with providers and the resources I found online were a bit fragmented. So, this blog is a way for me to share what I learned and hopefully help others (or just be a reference for myself in the future!</description></item><item><title>Using Terraform Providers: Dodging Default Behaviour</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2022-09-11-terraform-dodging-defaults/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2022-09-11-terraform-dodging-defaults/</guid><description>Contents Intro Providers: what are they? The easiest way to get started using a provider Adding version constraints Using multiple providers sharing the same name Using multiple versions of the same provider (spoiler: you can&amp;rsquo;t) Extra: configuring one provider binary multiple ways Downloading providers from places other than the public Registry Gist with example configs matching this article Conclusion &amp;amp; list of keywords Intro I&amp;rsquo;ve used Terraform regularly for a while now and decided to consolidate my knowledge by studying for the Terraform Associate Certification.</description></item></channel></rss>