<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frontend on Sarah French</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/tags/frontend/</link><description>Recent content in Frontend on Sarah French</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sarahfrench.dev/tags/frontend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fairy Lights</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/project/2020-06-01-fairy-lights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/project/2020-06-01-fairy-lights/</guid><description>This project was one of my earliest experiments with drawing vector images in illustration software and using them in a frontend project. This was done in ~June 2020.
I did a little write-up about how I completed this project on the page itself, so take a look at the project here: Fairy Lights on GitHub Pages</description></item><item><title>Conway's Game of Life</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/project/2019-11-28-game-of-life/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/project/2019-11-28-game-of-life/</guid><description>When? ~ November 2019
Where? Hosted React visualisation of the project
Code on GitHub
What? This project is an implementation of Conway&amp;rsquo;s Game of Life, a &amp;lsquo;game&amp;rsquo; that shows how a grid of cells that are either are alive or dead changes over time given: 1) a starting state of mixed cells, and 2) rule that define how a cells neighbours affects its status.
At the time I did this I was still doing my software development apprenticeship and only just learning about test-driven development.</description></item><item><title>Advent Calendar 2019</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/project/2019-08-27-advent-calendar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/project/2019-08-27-advent-calendar/</guid><description>What on Earth&amp;hellip; This, my friends, was the first &amp;lsquo;big&amp;rsquo; project I started and completed as a junior developer. It&amp;rsquo;s a advent calendar for 2019 which allowed the user (my boyfriend) to open up a new page each day between December 1st-25th, and each day is a little nugget of madness.
By having 25 advent pages to fill, this project gave me the opportunity to try a ton of new things and helped me learn SO MUCH about frontend development and browser APIs.</description></item></channel></rss>