<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Memos on Sarah French</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/memo/</link><description>Recent content in Memos on Sarah French</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sarahfrench.dev/memo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Viewports and broken media queries</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/memo/2024-06-23-viewports-and-broken-media-queries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/memo/2024-06-23-viewports-and-broken-media-queries/</guid><description>Just now I was struggling with writing a basic media query in some CSS. I&amp;rsquo;d reduced the problem down to just trying to get the background colour be red when the page was &amp;lt;700px wide when using the responsive preview developer tool in Chrome and it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t working, unless I made the max width much larger. Then a vague memory of &amp;ldquo;viewports&amp;rdquo; entered my mind&amp;hellip;
tl;dr add this to the &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; of your HTML and bear in mind viewports don&amp;rsquo;t always match the dimensions you&amp;rsquo;re presented as a viewer!</description></item><item><title>How to debug dependencies in Go projects</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/memo/2024-06-19-debugging-dependencies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/memo/2024-06-19-debugging-dependencies/</guid><description>Debugging dependencies If you want to debug how a dependency is used in a Go project run go mod vendor to download all your projects dependencies to a vendor folder in your project. You can then add breakpoints to the vendored code just like your project code.
Replacing dependencies with your forks If you&amp;rsquo;re working on a contribution to a dependency (for example fixing a bug you&amp;rsquo;ve discovered) then you might want to test that out locally with your project.</description></item><item><title>Why static assets might 404 unexpectedly in Hugo projects</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/memo/2024-06-02-hugo-image-assets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/memo/2024-06-02-hugo-image-assets/</guid><description>If you want to reference an image in the content of a Hugo website you cannot just add a new image to the static folder and hardcode the image&amp;rsquo;s src in markdown. Hugo will only include assets if they are used in Hugo templating, like {{ $go := resources.Get &amp;quot;image/go.jpeg&amp;quot; }}.</description></item></channel></rss>