<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog posts on Sarah French</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog posts on Sarah French</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Debugging Terraform providers with VS Code</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2024-05-28-debugging-terraform-providers-with-vscode/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2024-05-28-debugging-terraform-providers-with-vscode/</guid><description>My first experience of &amp;lsquo;debugging&amp;rsquo; was using good old console.log in JavaScript when I was first learning about programming. Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that print statements and logs only get you so far, and proper debugging is so much more useful. When I first started contributing to Terraform provider projects I wasn&amp;rsquo;t shown how to use debuggers with providers and the resources I found online were a bit fragmented. So, this blog is a way for me to share what I learned and hopefully help others (or just be a reference for myself in the future!</description></item><item><title>Using Terraform Providers: Dodging Default Behaviour</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2022-09-11-terraform-dodging-defaults/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2022-09-11-terraform-dodging-defaults/</guid><description>Contents Intro Providers: what are they? The easiest way to get started using a provider Adding version constraints Using multiple providers sharing the same name Using multiple versions of the same provider (spoiler: you can&amp;rsquo;t) Extra: configuring one provider binary multiple ways Downloading providers from places other than the public Registry Gist with example configs matching this article Conclusion &amp;amp; list of keywords Intro I&amp;rsquo;ve used Terraform regularly for a while now and decided to consolidate my knowledge by studying for the Terraform Associate Certification.</description></item><item><title>When is a leap year not a leap year? Don't ask Microsoft Excel</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2021-02-27-leap-year-excel-error/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2021-02-27-leap-year-excel-error/</guid><description>Dates and times always have the potential to cause trouble in code; back in my apprenticeship, my teacher drove this point home by sharing a great article called Falsehoods programmers believe about time. Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve been wary of working with data that relies heavily on dates. (If you cannot tell, this paragraph&amp;rsquo;s job is to supply foreshadowing).
In a recent project at work, I&amp;rsquo;ve been collecting Covid-19 data from various government sources and consolidating them into one standardised collection.</description></item><item><title>Hello World : Looking back on 2020</title><link>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2021-01-03-my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sarahfrench.dev/blog/2021-01-03-my-first-post/</guid><description>Hello! If you are reading this, welcome! You are probably one of my parents, my partner, or someone procrastinating by reading what will arguably be the worst blog post I write. But that is the point– I want to start blogging about tech and working as a developer to improve my writing.
To ease me into regular writing, and as a way to describe my background a little, here&amp;rsquo;s a little recap of my achievements in 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>